infinum.co 2018-08-16

# Infinum | App design & development | Infinum

## Who we are

Infinum is an independent design and development agency. We build powerful digital experiences that make businesses more efficient and people's lives easier. Our clients range from venture-backed startups to global enterprises. Our work is used by millions and has been recognized by trade and industry authorities such as Deloitte and Inc. 5000.

## Data protection philosophy

We are dedicated to keeping your personal information confidential. We do not sell, rent, or lease your data to third parties,we will not provide your personal information to any third party individual, government agency, or company at any time unless compelled to do so by law.

## Collecting, using, storing and sharing of your personal data

In some instances, we might collect your personal information:

### 1) Intent to collaborate on a project

Your personal info such as name, e-mail address and telephone number as well as other info you submit in description of your project, submitted into „Hire us“ form, will be stored and used only for business development purposes and only for the period of our negotiation process.

### 2) Intent to become an employee

When you submit your personal data into „Apply for career switch“ or „Apply for this position“ forms, they're going to be used solely for the job you're currently applying for, or the first position we think might fit your profile in case you're applying for unspecified position. We keep your data only during the job contest.

You can also choose that we keep your data for five years after closing the contest you're applying for. If something interesting pops up during that period, we'll drop you an e-mail. You can change this whenever by sending us an e-mail to [dpo@infinum.co](mailto:dpo@infinum.co).

For processing personal data for Infinum's recruitment purposes, we use a third party applicant tracking system designed to take care of your personal info with highest integrity developed by GREENHOUSE, USA, New York and San Francisco. Greenhouse will handle your data with respect and for more details, check out their [Privacy Policy](https://www.greenhouse.io/privacy-policy).

### 3) General inquiry via hello@infinum.co or contact@infinum.co

When you contact us for new business, employment, sponsorship , media inquiries or anything else via this e-mail address, we will first determine the nature of the inquiry. In case it contains personal information, we will process this information in the manner prescribed by these Rules for a particular type of personal data, or manner which is prescribed by law.

### 4) Newsletter subscriptions

When you enter your email address in the form to receive one of our newsletters, your email address will be used only for that specific purpose. You will receive updates from us until you make a withdrawal by clicking on the unsubscribe link at the bottom of each newsletter or by sending us an e-mail at [dpo@infinum.co](mailto:dpo@infinum.co).

For sending company-wide news and updates, we use a MAILCHIMP, Georgia, USA, service that will treat your data lawfully and carefully. Find out more in their [Privacy Policy](https://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy).

For sending our weekly tech newsletters (#DesignSlices, #iOSCocoaTreats, #RubyDrops, #AndroidSweets, #FrontendCookies), we use a CURATED, Memphis, USA service that will treat your data lawfully and carefully. Find out more in their [Privacy Policy](https://curated.co/eu-privacy).

### 5) Analytics

We use a third party service, Google Analytics, to collect standard internet log information and details of visitor behaviour patterns (e.g. number of visitors to the various parts of our web page) in a way which does not identify anyone. [More info](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en).

### 6) Remarketing and behavioural targeting

We use services that allow us to inform, optimize and serve advertising based on past use of our site. It is performed by tracking usage data and by using cookies, which is then transferred to the partners that manage the remarketing and behavioral targeting activity. We use Facebook custom audience, Twitter custom audience, and LinkedIn custom audience. 

### 7) Cookies

More information can be found in our Cookie Policy.

### 8) Social media contacts

If you send us a private or direct message via social media the message will be stored for period necessary to solve your request, but not longer than five years. We will first determine the nature of the inquiry, and in case it contains personal information, we will process this information in the manner prescribed by these Rules for a particular type of personal data, or manner which is prescribed by law.

Infinum has an official profile on the following social networks:

Facebook <https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation>  
LinkedIn <https://www.linkedin.com/legal/privacy-policy>  
Twitter <https://twitter.com/en/privacy#update>  
Instagram [https://help.instagram.com/155833707900388](https://help.instagram.com/155833707900388?helpref=page_content)  
YouTube <https://policies.google.com/privacy/update?hl=hr>  
GitHub [https://help.github.com/articles/github-privacy-statement](https://help.github.com/articles/github-privacy-statement/)  
Dribbble <https://dribbble.com/privacy>  
Meetup [https://www.meetup.com/privacy](https://www.meetup.com/privacy/)

### 9) Infinum public events participants 

We collect information such as your first name, last name, e-mail, to inform you about the event and ask for your feedback. We will not retain the data after the event is finished. However, we will ask you directly if you would like us to keep your data for the purpose of further cooperation. We use third party service Meetup to manage our public events. Your data will be processed legally and carefully, as noted in their [Privacy Policy Notice](https://www.meetup.com/privacy/).

### 10) Infinum Academy students 

We collect information such as your first name, last name, e-mail, phone, education and CV to assess your suitability for participation in Infinum Academy. We will not retain the data after the Academy is finished. However, we will ask you directly if you would like us to keep your data in case of future job opportunities, but not longer than five years.

### 11) Giveaways

After conducting a giveaway, we will use your personal information (name, last name and delivery address) solely for the purpose of the transaction. Your information will not be kept for more than five years. 

## Where we store your data

In order to deliver the services described by this policy, Infinum uses products provided by Amazon Web Services, Inc. (AWS). All products provided by AWS are compliant with ISO security standard 27018, delivering the highest level of information security. Personal data is collected and stored in data centres located within European Union. More information can be found in [AWS's Privacy Policy](https://aws.amazon.com/privacy) and [Data Privacy FAQ](https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/data-privacy-faq).

Any transfer of personal data to third parties listed in this policy happens over a secure connection.

No personal data is transferred to third parties or to third countries other than what's listed in this policy.

## How long do we retain information

We do not keep your data longer than necessary; all periods are specified in each category above.

## Information security

In order to protect data privacy, we implement physical, technical and administrative measures such as:

  * regular updating and testing our security technology;
  * implementing technology of highest security standards;
  * ensuring that our partners are GDPR compliant;
  * providing access to personal data only to authorized employees;
  * training employees about GDPR and taking appropriate disciplinary measures to enforce employees' privacy responsibilities.

## Data subject rights list

  1. Right of access (GDPR Article 15).
  2. Right to rectification (GDPR Article 16).
  3. Right to erasure or right to be forgotten with additional stipulations, among others if personal data has been made public (GDPR Article 17).
  4. Right to restriction of processing (GDPR Article 18).
  5. Right to be informed (GDPR Article 19).
  6. Right to data portability (GDPR Article 20).
  7. Right to object (GDPR Article 21).
  8. Right not to be subject to a decision based solely on automated processing, including profiling, which produces legal effects concerningor her or similarly significantly affects him or her (GDPR Article 22).

For more information and for executing you rights, please contact Infinum’s data protection officer at [dpo@infinum.co](mailto:dpo@infinum.co).

## Supervisory body

We are doing all that is within our power to make your experience with Infinum pleasant, and treat your information with highest integrity. We still are obliged to inform you that you have the right to contact the supervisory authority - the Personal Data Protection Agency (AZOP) in a chance of any misconduct.

You can find contact information for AZOP here: <https://azop.hr/zastita-podataka-hrvatska/detaljnije/kontaktirajte-nas>.
